disboards.com 2019-03-30

# DIS - Privacy Policy

It is important that our site visitors understand that any information you provide to us during the course of your visit to our site is NEVER sold or provided to any third party for any reason. The information collected is used ONLY for it's intended purpose. 

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our Service. By using the Service, you agree to our [ **Terms of Use**](http://www.wdwinfo.com/disclaimer.htm) and accept our collection, use, and disclosure practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree and consent, discontinue use of the Service.

**1\. What Personally Identifiable Information of Yours is Collected:**

Non Personal information for the purpose of determining the number of visitors to our site is captured every time you visit. This information includes the IP Address of your Internet Service Provider, the type of browser you are using, the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site. 

You can read more about how we use cookies and other third parties for wdwinfo.com [here](http://www.wdwinfo.com/cookies.htm) and disboards.com [here](http://www.wdwinfo.com/cookies-disboards.htm).

The ONLY time personal information about you is captured is when you provide that information to us in the form of a survey, newsletter, contest, contact us form, contributor application, discussion forum registration or chat forum registration. **

2.   What organization is collecting the information:

**

The information that you provide to us is collected and maintained by Werner Technologies, LLC., 4417 13th Street # 475 St Cloud, FL 34769  
**

3.   How is the information used:

**

The information is used only for the purpose it is intended.  Under no circumstances will your email address, or personal information be sold to any third party, at any time for any reason.  We will use the email information ONLY for issues that pertain to the area in which you provided the information.  For example, if we have plans to make changes to a contest, all those who registered for that program will receive an email outlining those changes.  If you have signed up for one of our mailing lists, only information pertaining to that mailing list is sent to you, along with clear and explicit instructions on how to unsubscribe from such a list.  At no time will you be solicited directly from the site unless you have acknowledged that you wish to receive such information. **

4.   With whom is the information shared:

**

The information is not shared with any other entity under any circumstance unless ordered by a court of law to do so. **

5.   What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information:

**

The only areas that require entry of any personal data are listed above.  You have the right not to participate in these forums if you do not wish to include your personal information.  You have the right not to not fill out any form on our website if you do not wish to to include personal information.  At any time, you can request that your information be removed by submitting a request to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) **

6.   Important Exceptions:

**

When you register to post on our discussion forums, you are given the option to display your email address for other site visitors to see.  If you opt to do that, we have no control over what mail you may receive as a result.  At that point, the information is considered 'published' with your permission.  You can still use our discussion forums and NOT display your email address by selecting that option during the registration process.

Also, when you sign up for a particular advertisers services (via the site), that advertiser may use your email address to provide you with information on their services. 

Participants should be aware that when you are on any web site, you could be directed to other sites when you click on an advertising banner. Clicking on an ad banner may take you off our site. The DIS wants you to be aware that other sites may send their own cookies to participants, collect data or solicit personal information over which we have no control. **

7\. COPA Compliance:

**

In compliance with the **Children's Online Privacy Act** , we affirm the following:

**Contact Information:**

Peter Werner, Owner  
Werner Technologies, LLC.  
4417 13th Street # 475   
St Cloud, FL 34769

**_Personal Information Collected:_** The only time personal information on the site may be collected by a person under the age of 13 years old, is if said child registers for use of our discussion board.  The discussion board does not ask for the users name, rather it requires the creation of a 'screen name' that the user determines.  It does provide for the entry of the users City and State, but these are not mandatory fields.  The information collected during the registration process is only to contact the user in the event that there is a problem with their use of the discussion forums, or if there are changes made to the forums that require notification.  Each user has the option to select NOT to be notified in such instances.  Under no circumstances is any information collected EVER provided to third parties.  Parents have the option to agree to the collection and use of the child's information without consenting to the disclosure of the information to third parties.

We do not require any participant, regardless of age, to provide more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in our discussion forums or chat rooms.

Parents have the right, under law, to request to view all personal information collected on their children and to request that it be deleted  from our records.  Parents also retain the right to refuse to allow further collection or use of the child's information. 

Any parent wishing to review this information, or requesting a deletion of that information should contact the webmaster of this site via email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**8\. Contact Us**.

We offer many ways to contact us. Those options can be found [here](http://www.wdwinfo.com/feedback.htm).
